<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ThingDefs>



  <!-- ============================ TestPawn ========================== -->

  <ThingDef ParentName="Human" Class="AlienRace.ThingDef_AlienRace">
    <thingClass>AlienRace.AlienPawn</thingClass>
    <defName>AlienTestPawn</defName>
    <label>alien test pawn</label>
    <description>A template Alien Pawn derived from a base human.</description>
    
  <!--========================== New entries ===========================-->
   
    <NakedBodyGraphicLocation></NakedBodyGraphicLocation>;
    The location of the body textures. If left empty the default human textures are used.
    Example: Things/AlienPawn/NakedBodies/

    <NakedHeadGraphicLocation></NakedHeadGraphicLocation>;
    The location of the head textures. If left empty the default human textures are used.
    Example: Things/AlienPawn/Heads/

    <DesiccatedGraphicLocation></DesiccatedGraphicLocation>;
    The location and graphic name of the remains texture. If left empty the default human textures are used.
    Example: Things/Pawn/Alien/AlienDessicated
    
    <CustomGenderDistribution>false</CustomGenderDistribution>
    Enables a custom distribution of genders among your pawns. Default is set to false.
    
    <MaleGenderProbability>0.5</MaleGenderProbability>
    If custom distribution is enabled, this value decides the proportions of males to females. 
    
    <PawnsSpecificBackstories>false</PawnsSpecificBackstories>
    If enabled, the FactionDef field backstorycategory is ignored, instead the same field in PawnKindDef is used instead.
    
    <HasHair>Vanilla</HasHair>,
    Defines the hair that is to be used. Default is Vanilla, meaning no changes to the hairgeneration.
    Alternatives:     Custom      Hair colors are decided by the alienpartgenerator
                      None        Pawns are created bald
    
    <GetsGreyAt>50</GetsGreyAt>;
    If HasHair is set to Custom, this value defines the average age at which your alien would get gray hair.
    
    <CustomSkinColors>false</CustomSkinColors>;
    Default is set to false. If set to true, the skincolor ist decided by the alienpartgenerator.

    <alienpartgenerator>
      
      <aliencrowntypes>
        <li>Male_Average_Normal</li>
      </aliencrowntypes>
      If a custom alien head path is defined, these are the graphic names from which a random head will be picked for the pawn.
      
      <alienbodytypes>
        <li>Male</li>
      </alienbodytypes>

      If a custom alien body path is defined AND you want to get away from the base body type distribution, these are the bodytypes from which a random one will be picked for the pawn.

    </alienpartgenerator>

    <alienskincolorgen Class="ColorGenerator_Options">
        <options>
          <li>
            <weight>10</weight>
            <only>RGBA(1.0,1.0,1.0,1)</only>
          </li>
        </options>
      </alienskincolorgen>   
    
      <alienhaircolorgen Class="ColorGenerator_Options">
        <options>
          <li>
            <weight>10</weight>
            <only>RGBA(1.0,1.0,1.0,1,1)</only>
          </li>
        </options>        
      </alienhaircolorgen>;

    Defines custom skin- and haircolors. Work the same as color options for items.

  </ThingDef>



</ThingDefs>